A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Publications, Paper records, RG 3, Series 1 FA1291
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IIE Networker, 2012-2015 (Box 41)
- IIE At A Glance, 2012, 2015 (Box 41)